DHIREN JUMMANI

Surat, Gujarat, India · +91 95747 08867 Email: dhiren.jummani.jhd@gmail.com

LinkedIn Profile: www.linkedIn.com/in/dhiren-jummani-ab6336114

Github: https://github.com/Dhiren003

Having an accomplished strategy and critical thinker with substantial experience in IT industry with ability in prototyping IT product by applying technical and business knowledge. I am particularly good at thinking problem based end-to-end solution.

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2019 – JUNE 2019 INTERN, D-LINK INDIA LTD., MUMBAI

JANUARY 2019 – PRESENT

CORE TEAM MEMBER, DSC, RNGPIT

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2017 – PRESENT

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING, COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

R. N. G. Patel Institute of Technology, Bardoli

JULY 2014 - MAY 2017

DIPLOMA ENGINEERING, COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Jayvantrai Harrai Desai Polytechnic, Palsana

MARCH 2014

SSC, L. P. SAVANI VIDYABHAVAN SCHOOL

SKILLS

- C/C++
- Java
- PHP
- Python
- Project Management
- Leadership
- Creativity

- Angular
- SQL
- Android
- Presentation
- Team Management
- Verbal Communication

INTERESTS

- Cloud Computing
- Data Analytics
- Node.js

- Machine Learning
- Artificial Intelligence
- React Native

CERTIFICATES

- Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure Coursera & DSC India
- Participant in Smart India Hackathon
- English Writing Proficiency AMCAT

PROJECTS

FEST MANAGEMENT SYSTEM (FEMSY), ONGOING

FEMSY is system which provides the digital platform for any events like Techfest, Workshops, Hackathons, etc. which will be easy for any organization to handle and have their records of it.

TECHFEST WEB & APP DEVELOPMENT, SEPTEMBER 2019

A web & app application was developed by me and my team for our college's techfest "Visvesmruti-2019"

More on: https://visvesmruti.tech/

TECHFEST WEB & APP DEVELOPMENT, SEPTEMBER 2018

A web & app application was developed by me and my team for our college's techfest "Visvesmruti-2018"

More on: http://visvesmruti18.fetr.ac.in/

GRIEVANCE REDRESSAL SYSTEM, NOVEMBER 2018

A web application was developed by me and Kuldip Patel (Classmate) for our college to get the queries of faculties, parents or students regarding to the college.

More on: http://grievance.fetr.ac.in/

VOLUNTARY COMMITMENTS

Visvesmruti – 2019: Core Member and Lead Web Developer of "Web & App Development" Team & Co-Ordinator of "Programming Date" Event.

Visvesmruti – 2018: Core Member of "Web & App Development" Team & Volunteer of "Programming Date" Event.